Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series V. Buildings and Facilities
  - FRANCE - Institut de'Hygiene, Strasbourg, France - wing used by the American Foot-and-Mouth Diseases Commission as an animal isolation ward; Commissioners: Dr. H.W. Schoening, Dr. Peter Olitsky, Dr. Jacob Traum, Undated (Box 45, Folder 49)
    Item number: 704
  - SCOTLAND - Moredun Institute, Edinburgh, Scotland, photo presented to Dean William A. Hagan by Prof J Russell Grieg, Undated (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - SCOTLAND - Farriery building of William Dick, Edinburgh, Scotland; Photo by Prof J Russell Grieg, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    Item number: 720.1
- Series VI. Calenders and Schedules
  - Activities Calendar, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Academic Calendars, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Class Schedules, 1974-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Exam Schedules, 1966-1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Clinic Assignments and Sections, 1962-1980,n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Activities Calendar, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Series VII. Committees and Boards
  - Standings Committees of the Faculty-List, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Council (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Task Force for Curriculum Review, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Cornell Veterinarian (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Centennial Sub-Committee - Commemorative Projects, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Committee, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Series VIII. Departments, Units, and Services
  - Anatomy Department (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Auto Tutorial Center, 1970's (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Auto Tutorial Center - Planning, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Avian and Aquatic Department (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Baker Institute (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Baker Institute - Conferences and Workshops (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Biomedical Communications, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Department of Clinical Sciences (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Clinical and Biomedical Science (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Diagnostic Laboratory (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Diagnostic Laboratory - Test and Fee Schedule, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Equine Clinic, etc., ca. 1980s (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Equine Research Park, 1963-ca. 1970s (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Farriery, 1955, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Feline Health Center (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Feline Health Center - Louis J. Calmuti Memorial Feline Consultation and Diagnostic Service, 1977-1981, 1991, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Department of Histology and Embryology, 1900-1918 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hospital (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hospital-Animal Behavior Clinic (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hospital/Clinics - Clinical Notes - Large Animal Surgery (8 volumes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
  - Hospital/Clinics - Clinical Notes - Small Animal Surgery (1 volume, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
  - Hospital/Clinics - Clinical Notes - Small Animal Medicine (3 volumes, 1896-1918 (Box 14)
  - Hospital/Clinics - Unidentified Large Animal Record Book, 1934-1941 (Box 14)
  - Laboratory Animal Diagnostic Resource, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory Animal Medicine (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory for Pregnancy and Newborn Research, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory of Veterinary Physiology and Pharmacology, 1904-1906 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory of Veterinary Physiology and Pharmacology, 1907-1910 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Large Animal Medicine,Obstetrics, and Surgery, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Annual Report on Reproductive Research
  - Large Animal Medicine, Obstetrics, and Surgery, ca. 1940's (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Course Bibliographies
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Danks, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    1 of 3
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Danks, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    2 of 3
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Danks, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    3 of 3
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Delahanty, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    1 of 2
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Delahanty, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    2 of 2
  - Department of Medicine (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Microbiology, Immunology, and Parasitology (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Molecular Medicine (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pathology (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Pathology - "Early post mortem notes before organization in 1917, and duplicates of later type-written noes", 1910-1920 (Box 20)
  - Physical Biology (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Physiology (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Zweig Memorial Fund for Equine Research (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Photographs and Slides
  - Ambulatory and Production Medicine - some slides, 1980s-2003 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Diagnostic Lab - slides, 1980s-2002 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Equine Hospital, no dates (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Farm Animal Hospital - some slides, 1980s-2000 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Series IX. Events and classes
  - Annual Conference (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Black Tie and Tails, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Black Tie and Tails, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Caliente y Frio: An Exhibit of Wildlife Art, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    By Fabian Martinez
  - Christmas Party (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Centennial-General, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Centennial Book-General, ca. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Centennial-Book-Decade Summaries, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Centennial-Book-Department and Organization Summaries, ca. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Centennial-Book-Notes from Faculty and Alumni (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Centennial-Book-Published Resources, ca. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Centennial-Time Capsule, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Commencement and Hooding (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Commencement and Hooding-Programs (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Honor Day (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Honor Day-Prizes-H.H. Dukes Prize-General, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Honor Day-Prizes-H.H. Dukes Prize-Donor Letters, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Open House (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Reunions (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Semi-Centennial, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Event Flyers to Open House, Exhibitions, James Law Distinguished Lecture Series, Commencement, and Caliente y Frio (Box 9)
  - Governors Citations (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1903,1907,1956,1960,1963 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971,1973,1975,1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1985,1987,1991 (Box 9)
  - Maps and Sketches of campus and facilities (Box 9)
  - Poster in memory for Franklin M. Loew (Box 9)
  - Cartoon Sketch (Box 9)
  - Place Cards for Honor Day - Caricature of the Faculty, by Vincent Paciello, 1940 (Box 16)
  - Place Cards for Honor Day - Animals, by Rebecca Gifford, 1940 (Box 17)
  - Millennium Time Capsule, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Photographs and Slides
  - Reunions, 1990s-2001 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Reunions, 1945 and 1990s (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Reunions, Various Dates (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Reunion - Class of 1951, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Reunion - Class of 1951, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Reunion - Class of 1951, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Reunion - Class of 1996, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Reunions - Classes of 1946, 1971, 1981, 1986, 1996, 2001, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Centennial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Centennial Room Dedication, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Equine Events - slides, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Events - Miscellaneous, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Open Houses, 1988, 1994, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Open House - some slides, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Open House - some slides, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Open House, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Open House, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - White Coat Ceremony, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - White Coat Ceremony, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - White Coat Ceremony, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Zweighalt Dedication, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Annual Conference, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Exhibits, 1915 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Exhibits, 1918 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Exhibits, 1911 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Students in anatomy (or postmortem) room in James Law Hall with dissected animals on trolleys; Prof. G.S. Hopkins standing under a standing student in center; human and dog skeletons on table at left., 1902 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Rows of students with faculty in front under portico of James Law Hall; James Law seated in center, 1903-05 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 3 rows of students in anatomy lab with Professor G.S. Hopkins in center., 1905 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Veterinary banquet, Feb. 15, 1905, Society of Comparative Medicine, on 10th anniversary of founding of the College., 1905 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 5 rows of students; with faculty in front center: Williams, Hopkins, Gage, Law, ?, Moore; Gift of Mrs. John F. Miller., 1906 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 4 rows of students in suits and jackets in anatomy lab in James Law Hall., 1906 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 2 rows of 12 students in suits. "Gift of Mrs. John F. Milk", 1906 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - 4 rows of students in anatomy lab; student on right has a "C" on his sweater; Professor G.S. Hopkins in center front., 1906 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - "Veterinary Class of 1907." -- Students at rows of tables in anatomy laboratory of James Law Hall with bones and parts of skeletons., 1907 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 3 rows of students in dark suits in front of ivy covered wall of James Law Hall. "Darby memorabilia given by Arthur North '35", 1907 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - "Veterinary Class of 1907" - Students in suits seated on either side of two long tables., 1907 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 3 rows of students in white; with 4 faculty in dark suits in front row; in anatomy lab with a horse skeleton on right., 1907 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - 6 rows of students outside under portico of James Law Hall; Florence Kimball is 2nd row, right; James Law is seated with other faculty in front, 1908-11 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - 6 rows of students outside under portico of James Law Hall; Florence Kimball is 2nd row, right; James Law is seated with other faculty in front, 1908-11 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "Class of 1910" - 3 rows of 25 students in white outside under portico of James Law Hall; Florence Kimball in seated in white coat; with 2 faculty in center: Hopkins and Sunderville., 1910 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - 4 rows of 29 students in white; with 4 faculty under James Law Hall portico: Miller, Hopkins, Sunderville, Frost, 1911 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Students in white with caps; a horse is upside down being dissected on the lawn in front of the Clinic buildings., 1912 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 4 rows of students in white; 3 faculty in 2nd row in dark suits, under James Law Hall portico., 1912 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 3 rows of students in dark suits, 1912 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 4 rows of students in suits., 1912 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - 4 rows of students in whites; a black dog is in the center; in front of James Law Hall, 1916 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - 4 rows of students in white; one student in first row center holding a black dog in front of James Law Hall. ' Photo taken in 1916., 1918-19 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - 4 rows of students in whites in front of James Law Hall., 1917 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 5 rows of students in whites in front of James Law Hall., 1917 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - 2 rows of students in whites in front of James Law Hall., 1920 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 2 rows of students in whites in front of James Law Hall., 1920 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - "Spring 1920" - 2 rows of students in dark suits outside James Law Hall., 1920 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 2 rows of students under James Law Hall portico; with faculty in front center: Udall, Fish, Gage, Moore, Williams, Hopkins., 1921 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 4 rows of students in dark suits; Prof. Donald W. Baker in back row center??, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - "NYS College Class of 1934"; 5 rows of students in whites; Professors Udall and Gibbons in lower right in front of the Clinics building., 1934 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - 4 rows of students in whites; with faculty in center in front of Clinic building., 1935 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - 7 rows of students in uniform overcoats in snow on steps of Bailey Hall?, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Company C. 2306th S.C.S.U. June 28, 1943-Oct. 16, 1943. Many rows of students in tan military uniforms with Co. C. flag in top center., 1943 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 5 rows of students in Willard Straight Hall., 1944,45,46 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 3 rows of students outside in front of Clinic building; faculty in front row, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 3 rows of students in suits indoors in front of large curtained windows; Dean Hagan seated in front row 4th from left, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - "Class of 1952"; 4 rows of students with faculty in front., 1952 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Large group of students with faculty under James Law Hall portico; Faculty in center include Gage, Williams; James Law is 3rd from left in 2nd row., n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Rows of men and women in ballroom at annual conference 1956 Dr. Francis H Fox on floor at right; Dr. Stephen J. Roberts on right., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 14 young men in uniform?; cross legged person in center holds a football., n.d. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - 2 rows of students in whites in front of Hall-Wilson Laboratory, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Students in pathology and bacteriology lab at benches, 1903 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Students in pathology and bacteriology lab at benches with fume hood in ceiling, 1903 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Students in amphitheater in James Law Hall; James Law seated next to Auzouz papier-mache horse model, 1905 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Surgery on a horse with students in white; James Law standing in white brimmed hat in center; Profession W.L. Williams 2nd from left in white cap hat. "Print made from a glass plate.", pre-1908 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Students dissecting horses in anatomy lab, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 14 students in Post-mortem room near James Law Hall, with animal body parts on trolleys., 1902? (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 20 students (include 3 women) in white with kymograph in a physiology class??, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Students studying in periodical reading in Flower Library on 2nd floor of James Law Hall, 1920s (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Ambulatory service -- 6 students are examing a pig on its side on a farm call on ambulatory service, 1960s? (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Ambulatory service -- 6 students are examining a pig on its side on a farm call on ambulatory service (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Errington (Dr James Frost's assistant) treating a large horse outside in a field with other men and horses present, Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Item number: 336.32
  - Dr. Errington (Dr James Frost's assistant) treating a large horse outside in a field, Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Item number: 336.321
  - Students helping Dr. Myron Fincher? Outside in field with IV therapy for a cow, Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Item number: 336.31
  - Dr Stephen Roberts (3rd from left) with students and 2 ambulatory cars outside Medical Clinic Building, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Item number: UP-7615-3
  - 6 students looking at a piglet on the ground, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Item number: UP-7615-1
  - Four students looking a supplies in medical case near ambulatory cars, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Supplies inside truck of ambulatory car, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Item number: 3392
  - Anatomy lab, class of 1943 January in James Law Hall, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Item number: 301
  - Anatomy lab in James Law Hall; Dr. Robert E Habel in lab coat (far right), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Anatomy lab in James Law Hall; students examining a cow, dog and horse, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Item number: 7615-30
  - Three students in white coats with Dr. Malcolm Peckham holding specimen in anatomy museum, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Howard E Evans with half glasses with students in anatomy lab, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Item number: 741023-31-25
  - Dr. John Cummings (left) with students and microscope, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Item number: A10212-8-29
  - Dr. John Cummings (left) looking into microscope with students, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Item number: 830404-11-6A
  - Professor with glasses in white coat clipping or dissecting tissues from a cow carcass for teaching anatomy, Undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Item number: 300
  - Professor with glasses in white coat clipping or dissecting tissues from a cow carcass for teaching anatomy viewed by five men standing in fedora hats, Undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Item number: 300+
  - Two students in anatomy class with dog skeleton, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-30-33
  - Rows of students at benches looking into microscopes, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-33-11
  - Students Pam Mayer and George Merrill dissecting a dog with skeleton nearby, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-21-26
  - Students Pat Widrick and Stanley Tuffini dissecting a dog with skeletons nearby, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-21-20
  - Student John Gross with horse hindlimb and specimen in view, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-34-24
  - Student examining the leg of a live horse in comparative anatomy lab; Professor Dr. Robert Habel seen under horse., 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-34-25A
  - Students Joe McQuade and Carolyn McMaster dissecting head of dog with diagram in book nearby, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-31-24
  - Students dissecting a dog with dog skeleton in foreground, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-21-23
  - Students Henry Jann and Paul Johnson holding skull of dog with human skeleton hanging behind, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-31-16
  - Student Stanley Truffini dissecting dog with partial skeleton in foreground, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-21-13
  - African-American student with bandana on head beside a microscope (no animals or specimens), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-10-23
  - Students Mary Wilkes and Allen Schoen looking through microscope at lab bench, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-33-34
  - Student Mary Evans looking through a microscope (no animals or specimens), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-33-36
  - Students Pat Evans, Gretchen Allen, Laurel Ellis looking through microscopes, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 741023-33-29
  - Student with cap featuring College seal with other students in dissection, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: A20503-1-34A
  - Students looking down doing dissection, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: A20503-1-33A
  - Student Rick Brower with model of cow and books, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: A20503-1-8A
  - Student Rick Brower (center) talking with others in anatomy lab (no animals or specimens), 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: A20503-1-18A
  - Student Rick Brower with cow model and book, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: A20503-1-11A
  - Two students pointing to dog skull, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: A20503-1-29A
  - Three students looking through double-headed microscope with one observing, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 83020402-8A
  - Student fingering dissection specimen, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 830204-8-28
  - Four students looking at specimen, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 830204-8-5
  - Two students studying diagram next to inflated model of cow stomachs, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 830204-8-17
  - Two students at microscope looking a text of dissection manual, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 840107-S42-33
  - Three students point to skeleton of hindlimb of horse, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Item number: 840107-41-7
  - Four students with an open anatomy book, Undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Original anatomy lecture amphitheater (empty) in James Law Hall with Auzoux horse model, 1906 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Item number: 311.31
  - Class of students seated in anatomy lecture amphitheater with Dr James Law seated in center and Auzoux horse model, 1898 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Item number: 3-170-86
  - Dr. Samuel Burnett at table in old laboratory on westside of top floor of James Law Hall, 1900 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Dr Veranus Moore with headcap in microbiology lab of Main Building (James Law Hall), 1900 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 222.8
  - Diagnostic laboratory in Moore Lab; Dr. Thomas Benson (left), client in suit, and Mr. Johnson (technician) right), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Medical making and wash room group in Moore Lab; Mrs. Kraft, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Diagnostic lab staff at lab benches: Louise Barr, Ernest Beberstein, E Neil, Moore, Charlie Reid, Charlie Kincher, Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 7615-24
  - Rabies examination in Moore Lab, Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Herbert Gilman (left with glasses) and Dr. Hugh Stuart Cameron (right) in diagnostic lab in Main Building (James Law Hall), Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 312
  - Dr William E Evans necropsying a dead animal in the diagnostic lab in Moore Lab, Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 355.3
  - Dr N Bruce Haynes with mice in lab equipment vessels, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 8717-3
  - Dr N Bruce Haynes with lab equipment, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 8717-1
  - Scientist at bench with rows of test tubes (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 21-1156
  - Dr Sang Shin putting rack of test tubes in cooler, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 761001-15-31
  - Dr Sidney Nussbaum (right) with Dr. Brian Summers (2nd from left) and Dr. Greis in diagnostic lab, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Dr George Maylin (right) talking with President and Mrs Dale Corson (left) about Equine Drug Testing, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Item number: 731207-2-20
  - Lewis Williams setting up plate for rapid testing for Bang's disease (bovine brucellosis), 1942 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Technician/student putting chicken into gas chamber in James Law Hall, Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 316.1
  - Three scientistis in laboratory, Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 317
  - Technician putting white chicken in chamber, Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 317.1
  - Technician putting white chicken in chamber II, Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 317.11
  - Technician next to enclosed fume chamber, Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 317.12
  - Technician facing left in laboratory with test tube rack, Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 317.13
  - Technician facing right in lab with pipette, Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 317.14
  - Clinician recording EEG readings on medical record, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 780407-6-26A
  - Three scientists in white coats in lab, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 4-399-74
  - Three clinicians in lab with iquana in terrerium, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 741023-16-18
  - Scientist with test tubes and analytic equipment, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 780407-5-6A
  - John Blizzard and Dr Wang (grad student) in laboratory holding test tube, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: A30103-57-14
  - Fred Austin Linda Abenanty, Chuck Allen in physiology laboratory with equipment, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Item number: 741023-8-13
  - Veterinary students (Dr Donald Schlafer white shirt mustashe on right) in class in Lecture Hall III in the Veterinary Research Tower, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Veterinary students in classroom in Moore Lab (John Rapp, Morley Kare, Jack Lowe, Bill Medway), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Item number: 7615-27
  - Dr. Francis Fox lecturing on ophthalmology in veterinary students in class of 1957 in Medical Building upstairs lecture hall, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 5)